Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Buildings and Grounds Records 1892-1965
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Department of Building and Grounds, 1892-1932
  - Subseries 3: Individual Buildings
    - Tower Group, Organ and chimes (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Walker Museum (H. I. Cobb, 1893), Specifications, mechanical (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Whitman Laboratory (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1926), Specifications, general (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Whitman Laboratory, Specifications, mechanical (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Wieboldt Hall (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1928), Specifications, general (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Wieboldt Hall, Specifications, general (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Wieboldt Hall, Specifications, mechanical (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Wieboldt Hall, Planning, 1925-1928 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Wieboldt Hall, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Wieboldt Hall, Symbolism, models, inscriptions (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Wychwood, Lake Geneva, Wisc. (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1909), Specifications, house and boathouse (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Wychwood, Lake Geneva, Wisc., Specifications, service building (Robert C. Spencer, Jr., n.d.) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Yerkes Observatory (H. I. Cobb, 1895), Specifications, general (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Yerkes Observatory, Specifications, repairs and alterations (1908) (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Yerkes Observatory, Specifications, repairs to 90-ft. dome (1923-1927) (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Yerkes Observatory Faculty Houses (H. I. Cobb, 1896), Specifications, general, Zoology Building, SEE Hull Biological Laboratories (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 4: Catalogs and Letterheads
    - Air conditioning (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Architects (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Building materials (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Church organs, chimes, cushions, tablets (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Decorating: floors, walls, windows (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Electrical equipment and lighting (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Elevators (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Furniture and equipment (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Glass (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Greenhouses (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Hardware (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Landscaping (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Photographers (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Plumbing (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Power plant equipment (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Small houses (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Series II: Department of Building and Grounds, 1932-1965
  - Subseries 1: Buildings, A-H
    - Accelerator Building (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1951), see also Research Institutes, Planning, 1946-1949 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Accelerator Building, Furniture and equipment (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Accelerator Building, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Accelerator Building, Proton Target Station, 1954-1958 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Accelerator Building, Damage to Physical Sciences Shop, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Accelerator Building, Alterations, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Administration Building (Holabird, Root and Burgee, 1948), Planning, 1943-1948 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Administration Building, Furniture and equipment (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Administration Building, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Administration Building, Publicity (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - American Bar Center (Holabird and Root, 1954), Addition, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - American Meat Institute, SEE Eye Research Laboratories Animal Behavior Laboratory (Burnham and Hammond, 1961), Planning, 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Animal Behavior Laboratory, Specifications, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Animal Behavior Laboratory, Costs, Argonne Cancer Research Hospital, SEE Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute Center for Continuing Education, SEE Graduate Student Residence (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Chancellor’s House, Alterations (Shaw, Metz and Dolio, 1949) (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Chancellor’s House, Alterations and furnishing, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration (Zantzinger, Borie and Medary, 1937), Planning, 1936-1938 (Box 37, Folder 6-8)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Progress reports, 1937-1938 (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Furnishing and decorating (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Ornamental iron (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Models (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Costs (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Addition and alterations (Shaw, Metz and Dolio, 1962), planning, 1956-1961 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Addition and alterations, progress reports, 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Addition and alterations, structural investigation report, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Addition and alterations, groundbreaking, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Addition and alterations, landscaping (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Charles E. Merriam Center for Public Administration, Addition and alterations, costs, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 13-14)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Building (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1958), Planning, 1956-1958 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Building, Floor plans (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Building, Furnishing and decorating (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Building, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Building, Cornerstone (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Building, Plaques and inscriptions, Computation Center, SEE Research Institutes (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Cummings Life Sciences Center (I. W. Colburn and Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1970), Proposed quadrangle, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Cummings Life Sciences Center, Planning, 1957-1961 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Eye Research Laboratories (American Meat Institute, Burnham and Hammond, 1949), Planning, 1940-1949 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Eye Research Laboratories, Equipment (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Eye Research Laboratories, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Housing, 6011 Ingleside Avenue (Philip B. Maher, 1949), Planning, 1929-1947 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Housing, 6011 Ingleside Avenue, Architects’ specifications and contracts (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Housing, 6011 Ingleside Avenue, General specifications (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Housing, 6011 Ingleside Avenue, Mechanical and electric specifications (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Fire Alarm System, Report, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Harper Memorial Library (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1912), Alterations (Burnham and Hammond, 1962-1964) (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Hospitals and Clinics
    - Billings Hospital (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1927), alterations (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1949-1964), Planning, 1947-1957 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Plaques, inscriptions (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - O Billings Hospital, alterations, rthopedic clinics, Package 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Miscellaneous, Package 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Surgical, urology, ear nose and throat clinics, Package 3 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Outpatient lobby, Package 4 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Animal quarters, Package 7 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Air conditioning auditorium and autopsy room, Package 9 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, M-1 and A-1 corridor, superintendent’s office, Package 10 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Men’s and women’s toilets, Package 10a (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Surgery clinic, Package 11 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Basement cafeteria, Package 13 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, A-4 corridor, chest surgery, Package 14 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, M-1 corridor and adjacent work, Package 15 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Gift shop, lobby, Package 16 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Morgue, Package 17 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Pharmacy, Package 19 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Cafeteria air conditioning, Package 20 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Photographic area, Package 20a (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Nurses station W3, Package 23 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Vendomatic and security office, Package 24 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Intensive care wing, Package 26 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Outpatient psychiatric clinic, Packages 27 and 27a (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Microbiology, Package 29 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Air conditioning feasibility study, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Air conditioning feasibility study, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Billings Hospital, alterations, Air conditioning feasibility study, 1956-1962 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Billings Hospital Court Building (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1951), Planning, 1948-1951 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Billings Hospital Court Building, Estimates, costs (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Billings Hospital Court Building, Progress reports, 1949-1951 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Billings Hospital Court Building, Publicity (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Billings Hospital Court Building, Service entrance (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Billings Hospital Court Building, Transformer vault remodeling (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Bobs Roberts Hospital (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1930), Alterations, 1958-1960 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Chicago Home for Incurables (Chronic Disease Hospital, Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1961), Planning, 1958-1961 SEE ALSO Young Memorial Building (Box 43, Folder 11-13)
    - Chicago Home for Incurables, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Home for Incurables, Progress reports, 1959-1961 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Home for Incurables, Equipping and decorating (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Home for Incurables, Plaque (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Home for Incurables, Landscaping (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Home for Incurables, Publicity (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Home for Incurables, Alterations, 1961-1963 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1931), Alterations, 1953-1956 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Mothers’ Aid Pavilion alterations, planning, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Mothers’, estimates, costs, funding (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Mothers’, furnishing and decorating (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Mothers’, publicity (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Mothers’, plaques (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Chronic Disease Hospital, SEE Chicago Home for Incurables Country Home for Convalescent Children, Re-designation of funds and memorial plaque (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute (Argonne Cancer Research Hospital, Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1953), Planning, 1947-1952 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute, Arthur D. Little, Inc., report, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute, Government contract, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute, Subcontracts (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute, Progress reports, 1949-1953 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute, Equipment (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute, Models (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute, Alterations, 1956-1958 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute, Additions and alterations, 1960-1962 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Goldblatt Memorial Hospital (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1950), Planning, 1946-1951 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Goldblatt Memorial Hospital, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Goldblatt Memorial Hospital, Progress reports, 1948-1950 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Goldblatt Memorial Hospital, Equipping and furnishing (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Goldblatt Memorial Hospital, Plaques and inscriptions (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Goldblatt Memorial Hospital, Cornerstone (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Goldblatt Memorial Hospital, Publicity (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Goldblatt Pavilion, Outpatient Department (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1961), Planning, 1957-1959 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Goldblatt Pavilion, Outpatient Department, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Goldblatt Pavilion, Outpatient Department, Furnishing and decorating (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Goldblatt Pavilion, Outpatient Department, Plaques and inscriptions (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Goldblatt Pavilion, Outpatient Department, Landscaping (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Goldblatt Pavilion, Outpatient Department, Groundbreaking and dedication (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Hicks-Gilman Smith Hospital (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1953), Planning, 1936-1953 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Hicks-Gilman Smith Hospital, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Hicks-Gilman Smith Hospital, Progress reports, 1951-1953 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Hicks-Gilman Smith Hospital, Equipping, furnishing, decorating (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Hicks-Gilman Smith Hospital, Ornament, tablet, bust (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Hicks-Gilman Smith Hospital, Memorial agreements (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Home for Destitute Crippled Children (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1929), Alterations, 1958-1959 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Proposed Patient Hotel, Plans and estimates, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Buildings, J-R
    - Jones Chemical Laboratory (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1929), Proposed alterations and additions, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Kent Chemical Laboratory (Henry Ives Cobb, 1894), Alterations, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Laird Bell Law Quadrangle (Eero Saarinen and Associates, 1959, Planning, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Midway Plaisance, Underground parking (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Midway Studios (Pond and Pond, 1910; Otis F. Johnson, 1929), Remodeling, 1963-1965 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - National Opinion Research Center (5720 Woodlawn, Myron Hunt, 1897), Remodelling plans, 1958-1961 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - National Opinion Research Center, Costs (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - National Opinion Research Center, 6030 Ellis (Hausner and Macsai, David Swan, 1966), planning, 1963-1965, Orthogenic School, SEE Sonia Shankman Orthogenic School (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Psychology Building (Kelly, Beecher, Green, Henry Ives Cobb, 1893, 1899), Alterations, planning, 1961-1965 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Psychology Building, Application for National Science Foundation grant, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Psychology Building, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Psychology Building, Progress reports (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Psychology Building, Furnishing (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Quadrangle Club (Howard Van Doren Shaw, 1922), Refurbishing, 1956-1962 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Radar Station, Installation at 5801 Dorchester, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Research Institutes (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1951), Planning, 1945-1952 (Box 49, Folder 3-4)
    - Research Institutes, Costs (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Research Institutes, Progress reports, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Research Institutes, Furnishing and equipping (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Research Institutes, Publicity (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Research Institutes, Low Temperature Laboratory (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1957), planning (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Research Institutes, Low Temperature Laboratory (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1957), estimates, costs, funding (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Research Institutes, Computation Center (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1961), planning, 1950-1959 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Research Institutes, Computation Center, estimates, costs, funding (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Research Institutes, Computation Center, progress reports, 1959-1961 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Research Institutes, Computation Center, publicity (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Research Institutes, Computation Center, basement extension, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 4: Residences and Facilities for Students
    - Faculty Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Fraternities, 1962-1963 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Student Residence (Center for Continuing Education, Edward Durrell Stone, 1963, Planning, 1957-1961 (Box 50, Folder 8-10)
    - Graduate Student Residence, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Student Residence, Furnishing and fitting (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Student Residence, Groundbreaking and dedication (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Student Residence, Landscaping (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Student Residence, Publicity (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Married Student Housing, Proposal by Harry Weese and Associates, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Phemister Hall (Burnham and Hammond, 1959), Planning, 1955-1960 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Phemister Hall, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Phemister Hall, Progress reports, 1958-1959 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Phemister Hall, Plaque (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Pierce Hall (Harry Weese and Associates, 1960), Planning, 1957-1962 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Pierce Hall, Progress reports, 1958-1960 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Pierce Hall, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Pierce Hall, Housing and Home Finance Agency correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Pierce Hall, Furnishing, equipping, decorating (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Pierce Hall, Landscaping (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Pierce Hall, Publicity (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Pierce Hall, Groundbreaking (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Women’s Residence (Zantzinger, Borie and Medary, 1932, never built), Planning, 1928-1932 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Women’s Residence, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Woodward Court (Women’s Residence, Eero Saarinen and Associates, 1958), Planning, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Woodward Court, Planning, Holabird, Root and Burgee, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Woodward Court, Planning, Eero Saarinen and Associates, 1954-1956 (Box 52, Folder 9-10)
    - Woodward Court, Estimates, costs, funding (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Woodward Court, Furnishing, specifications (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Woodward Court, Furnishing, Saarinen schedule (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Woodward Court, Furnishing, 1956-1965 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Woodward Court, Landscaping (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Woodward Court, Dining halls (Woodward Commons) (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Woodward Court, Dining halls (Woodward Commons) furnishing (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Woodward Court, Lounge and head suite alterations, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Woodward Court, Publicity (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Woodward Court, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 5: Buildings, S-Y
    - Social Service Administration Building (Ludwig Mies van der Rohe, 1964), Estimates, costs, funding (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Social Service Administration Building, Furnishing (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Sonia Shankman Orthogenic School (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1917: alterations, Shaw, Metz and Dolio, 1951), Planning, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Sonia Shankman Orthogenic School, Costs (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Sonia Shankman Orthogenic Schoo,l Furnishing and decorating (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Sonia Shankman Orthogenic School, Cornerstone, Stagg Field, SEE West Stands (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Temporary Buildings, Arrangements for, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Tower Group (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1901), Remodeling (Harry Weese and Associates, 1965) (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - University High School (Perkins and Will, 1960), Planning, 1955-1957 (Box 54, Folder 9-11)
    - University High School, Planning, 1958-1960 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - University High School, Estimates, costs (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - University High School, Furnishing and equipping (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - University High School, Landscaping (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - University High School, Scammon Court (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - University High School, Temporary Gymnasium (James Gamble Rogers, 1903), demolition, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - University High School, Plaques (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - University High School, Dedication (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - University High School, Publicity (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - University High School, Architects’ statement of purpose (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - University High School, Architects award (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Walker Museum (Henry Ives Cobb, 1893), Alterations, 1956, 1963, planning (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Estimates, costs, funding (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - West Stands (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1913), Alterations for Institute of Metals, 1946 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - West Stands, Demolition, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Young Memorial Building (Chicago Home for Incurables, Burling and Whitehouse, 1888), Plans for future use, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 6: Building Trades, Furniture and Equipment Brochures
    - Blinds (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Clocks (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Dispensers and vendors (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Electrical equipment (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Elevators (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Fences (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Filters (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Floors (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Furniture (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Kitchen equipment (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Laboratory equipment (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Lettering (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Lighting (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Plaques (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Plumbing (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Pumps (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Roofing (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Smoking equipment (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Sterilizers (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Temperature control (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Trucking and lifting (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Ventilation (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Walls, doors, partitions (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Windows (Box 57, Folder 14)